

PROFILE

My name is David Duarte, Software Engineer and Fullstack developer with more than 4 years of experience in web application development, I have advanced knowledge in Html, Css, JavaScript, Typescript, I also have experience in relational and non-relational databases, managing version control with GIT and cloud media management with Cloudinary. My main focus is to create efficient and scalable solutions that meet customer requirements and provide an exceptional user experience.

CONTACT

Phone:

+57 3113466330

Portfolio:

https://portfolio-five-lime-79.vercel.app/

LinkedIn:

(2) David Duarte | LinkedIn

Email:

davemm.ku@gmail.com

Github:

davemmWeb (David Duarte)
(github.com)

HOBBIES

Program Reading Running Learning

DAVID DUARTE

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

EDUCATION

POLITECNICO GRAN COLOMBIANO

Software engineer Jan 2018 – Jun 2023

MORE COURSES:

BOOTCAMP SOY HENRY

Full Stack Web Developer

SENA

APPLICATION OF THE SCRUM FRAMEWORK FOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT PROJECTS

WORK EXPERIENCE

Freelance – Full stack

Development of web applications:

- Front with Next.js, Angular, MUI, Vue.
- Back with MongoDB, Laravel

Nov 2022 – today's date

Socioextrategico - Full stack

Analysis, design and development of web applications:

- Front with React, Redux, Tailwind
- Back with Node.js, Postgres, Sequelize
- Cloud file management with Cloudinary

Feb 2020 - Nov 2022

Freelance - Developer Frontend

Design, layout of web applications using Javascript, HTML, Css, Bootstarp.

Nov 2017 – Jan 2020

SKILLS

